For those of you trying to understand my ideology, trying to get on board with what it is I'm talking about when I be talking.
Here is Black Panther H. Ratt Brown saying in the 1960s what I'm still saying here in the 2020s.
Better way to enslave a man than give him the vote and call him free.
It does not profit black people or poor people anything to have the vote and not be able to select the candidates who they want to choose.
How can you choose between London, Johnson, Nixon, Agnew, Wallace, and Huffington?
There is no choice. Evil is evil. There's nothing in between that.
There were some lesser candidates. Gregory was running for office.
Others, Cleaver.
I think the vote can only be used as a tool of organization. We can only use the vote to organize our people.
Now, to really believe that we can put someone in office and that these people would be responsive to our needs is naïve, politically naïve.
Because even if one of the black candidates who ran for office were to take the office of president, then black people must be prepared to fight against that person.
Why?
Because, you see, the system mandates the action of the individual. The individual does not determine how this country will function.
This country works off the military-industrial complex, which means that it's profitable to wage war.
And unless you, you know, devise another plan or another scheme to sustain or to boost this economy, then it's going to be necessary to wage war.
Whether, you know, a black individual is in office or a white individual is in office.
Well, we're talking about a complete, a change in system.
They want to stand in the way of every move forward.
The only way you can think about your people's struggle is when you are involved in your people's struggle.
We're going to have to change how we relate to each other as human beings.
We're going to fight in solidarity.
Unity.